All right. Who's popping it off?
>> So, so right out of the box here, you've
you've played against this team a number
of times in a rivalry, like what's it
like switching sides like this?
>> No, it's amazing. It's funny because
I've always actually been a fan of like
the culture and how competitive they
were. Um, so being a part of it now, I'm
excited to join that competitive spirit.
Um, but it's crazy. It's crazy. Uh,
obviously them over there, they're like,
man, they're mad. The fans are mad and
stuff like that. But, uh, just part of
the game and opportunity present itself
and I'm excited to be here. But, it's a
it's a unique situation, but it's time.
It's time.
>> You're no stranger to talented wide
receiver rooms, but you join Mike and
Marv and of course Trey at the tight end
spot. What's your feeling going into
this officially?
>> I'm super excited, man. Uh, I actually
met Wilson after the game when he went
for 200. I was like, I had to just go up
to him and just give him his flowers. I
was like, bro, I don't know where you
came from, but like that was phenomenal.
and he followed me on socials and stuff
like that. So, connected with him. Been
a fan of Marv since college. McBride is
just a beast. The way he was talking out
there on the field when we were
competing, um, I just love seeing all
that stuff. So, being a fan of the game,
I I, you know, I see people and now to
be teammate with these guys, um, I'm
just here to bring some energy to them,
help them grow, and I know they're going
to help me grow. So, I'm excited.
>> What was it about the culture and
everything here that caught caught your
attention? When did it catch your
attention? Why did it catch your
attention? So, I think it was my first
stint in San Francisco. We It was Larry
Fitzgerald. I think they he had a
game-winning catch, I think. I don't
know what year it was, but it was crazy.
And that's when I was like, "Okay, yeah,
Arizona, they're different. It's always
competitive when we come into the
stadium when they come to us." So,
that's something that I always noticed.
So, that was the specific game. I don't
know what specific game it was, but I
know it was a gamewinner by Larry, the
legend. Um, and so that's when it kind
of started. But, I've always, you know,
been competing um with this team. team
and so to be a part um I'm excited to
see where this journey goes.
>> You posted on on social media kind of
your excitement um to be here kind of
what what went into that and why were
you so excited?
>> Yes, obviously Mike Laflur that's my
guy. Um he's he helped me so much my
rookie year. um he actually was one of
the people that brought me into the
league and so um he developed me well uh
in in the receiver room and we just had
a strong connection, strong relationship
and that's what I've been um taking
pride in is building relationship with
people and uh it's it's helped me this
far. So um he's somebody that I I'm very
close to and I'm passionate about. So
I'll run through a wall for that guy.
You know what I'm saying? I'll go over
the middle. I four, five block, eight,
nine block, whatever I got to do to to
help the team and help him um start his
his head coaching career off right. So
that's that was my main passion and uh
that's and and obviously the
organization. It's it stands for itself.
You know what I'm saying? When I said
the competitive spirit and and what it's
built and I want to help build that some
more.
>> You mentioned the energy a couple times.
You obviously have a lot of it.
[laughter] We've seen it on social
distance just where does that come from?
Is that just always been you?
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, it's a great question.
It's it's it's my as my my perspective
of life. Um I'm [clears throat] in year
going to year 10 to even have this
opportunity for the organization to
welcome me in. Mike welcoming me in like
I'm I'm honored. You know what I'm
saying? Like I don't take it for
granted. So it's even more passion now
where I'm at because they try to push
you out, you know? So to be welcomed in,
it's it's honoring. And so that's how
I've been my whole career is playing
with that chip and really enjoying it
because you know I it's what they say
I'm not supposed to be here. So if I can
play with that passion and and show that
I really enjoy it, people notice and and
it's something that's helped me
throughout my career.
>> You were with Michael Flur early in his
NFL coaching career when he was a wide
receivers coach. What was he like as a
young wide receivers coach in San
Francisco?
>> Yeah, Mike [clears throat] Mike was
special to me. Um you can tell he knows
the game and that's what's special. Um,
obviously there's a lot of trees
connected. Shanahan, different trees.
You see Shawn McVey, his brother Matt
Laflur, they all are kind of from the
same tree. And so it's just special how
they're all connected and what they
know. So, it's just awesome that
opportunities create theirel and that's
what's happening with Mike and uh he's
just helped me understand the game from
a different perspective, you know,
playing a role or cuz when I was
younger, I was coming in off the bench
and going on third down and he had to
get me prepared for that and it's really
everything's on me. If I don't catch
this third down, we get off the field.
So, I'm a young rookie secondyear guy
like with that kind of pressure and he
allowed that pressure to be like not so
heavy on me. You know what I'm saying? I
was going in with confidence because of
what he was teaching me. And so for him
to get to where he's at, going from
receiver, coach, OC, building up, um,
it's it's not a fluke. It's it's what he
deserves.
>> You're coming from an organization
that's won a lot, that's knew how to
win.
>> Yeah.
>> Going to an organization that just has
not won a lot. What can you bring from
your time there and help the culture
here like learn how to win?
>> Absolutely. And then when you guys ask
about the white outs, you know, I just
want to bring that energy into the room.
I want Marv to feel the energy from me
that I'm enjoying it. Wilson to feel it
too. Every everybody in the building to
to feel that I'm passionate about it,
that I want to bring something to the
team, whatever it is, whether it's plays
on the field, energy off the field,
whatever that role is. Um just finding
it and maximizing it, you know, and
that's what I'm excited about. And I
know the culture has been built well.
And so little pieces here and there, and
that's what organizations do. So I feel
like they're making the right moves,
bringing in certain people, and it takes
time. So hopefully it's it's it's rapid
with me here. But uh that's kind of my
idea of just doing what I'm supposed to
do. Um being who I am and I know it's
beneficial because it's it's done things
for me to get here.
>> What's your approach then? I mean you're
the new guy, but then also you're the
guy that's coming in with the most
experience with the new head coach play
caller. Do you take on an immediate
leadership role in your eyes?
>> Absolutely. Yeah. Mike, um, you know, we
have good conversations and, uh, just
talking about, you know, I am the bet in
the room and I got to carry that and I
and I I take pride in that and honor in
it and how I work every day, how I
approach it. Uh, I've learned so much of
how to train, how to take care of my
body, of how to operate within the
building, building relationships, all
those things play a factor into playing
football. So, I can't just be a football
player. I have to learn my OC. I have to
learn, you know, how the defense thinks,
you know, just building those
relationships. Some young guys may not
understand that they don't want. Some
guys may not want to talk or like
engage. And if I can help somebody come
out of that shell, embrace the the
connection on the team. That's going to
help the team be better. So, that's
something that I take pride in as a
leader in the room and uh just off the-
field stuff, doing right with your
money, little things, you know, that
I've learned. I've done bad with money.
I've not trained sometimes and had bad
results. So, I've learned from all my
situations just to help somebody else.
You're obviously very in tune with what
goes on off the field, on the field. In
what ways do you think your play style
can mesh well with this offense?
>> That's a great question. So, Mike is
that's the power of me and Mike's
relationship, and that's why I'm big on
relationships. So, I know the system. I
know exactly what he's thinking, where
he wants me to be, timing, and things
like that. So, getting open. I pride
myself on one-on-one. So, like, I don't
know when it's going to present itself
because there's zone, man. But how how
Mike displays it and how he draws it,
I'm gonna understand. So I'm gonna know,
all right, I need to be right here at
eight steps at this timing and if I do
that, it's going to be a successful
play. Help the quarterback read it
right, run the route, right? Um it's
just it kind of basic football, but um
wherever I fit in and wherever the plan
is, I don't really know yet. So like I
got to compete. I got to work my way in.
Not just coming here to just think I'm
the guy, you know? I'm I'm ready to earn
it and and earn the fans respect, your
guys respect, organizations respect, and
that comes with making plays. So, when I
get that first catch, man, it's going to
be it's going to feel good. But, uh,
that's kind of how I see myself, just
plug and play wherever Mike may need me.
If it's outside, inside, I know I got
that versatility. So, just playing with
confidence and competing at a high
level. When you compete, you give
yourself a best chance to to do good.
>> In order to get that first catch, you
need to get the ball. Absolutely. when
you looked at the situation here,
[clears throat]
>> quarterback. How did you evaluate kind
of what was happening on the court?
>> No, that's that's a great question, man.
It's um that's just every organization
situation, you know, they're trying to
find the guy and that's that's what it
is. So, my biggest thing was Mike in the
space that I was at and I'm like, I
trust you, Mike. I don't care if you
don't have a quarterback. I don't care
if you don't have a whole line. I trust
you and I know what you're going to
build and if I'm a piece to that puzzle,
hey, add me now and you can deal with
the quarterback situation later. And so
it didn't really concern me because it
comes down to timing and if I can get
open and the O line can block, we're
going to move the ball. But if we can't
block and I don't run good routes and
run it at the right timing, we're not
going to do anything. So the pieces come
together. So I wasn't really too
concerned. Um Gardner is a great
quarterback, Jacobe great quarterback.
So draft coming up, never know what's
going to happen, but um I just believe
in my abilities. I believe in the team
abilities and I think that's going to
fix any problem that we might deal with.
>> Have you joined anybody from that room
yet?
>> From the receiver room.
>> From the quarterback room.
>> Oh, I I met Gardner today. Um I ran past
him. I was the last guy here. Y'all
might know that. But [laughter] I saw
him a little earlier. Connected with
him. That was my first time meeting him.
I've always been a fan of him. Huge
competitor. And uh that competitive
spirit is something that I um connect to
really well. coming to a new team, how
beneficial is it to have that
relationship already established with
Mike when it comes just hitting the
ground running?
>> Yo, it's that's that's everything, you
know, relationships are everything. And
um Mike uh Mike was It's so funny
because right when the Tamron period
opened, he hit me up like, "Hey, what
you thinking?" And I'm like, "Hey, bro,
you you let me know. I'm waiting for you
in a sense." And so we got that good
relationship and um but it's it's
exciting. I don't have to struggle with
trying to learn new formations. like it
may be different terms and he may have
different ways of calling things now
from our past, but I know it's going to
be similar and it's going to be
something I can pick up on and hit the
ground running.
>> Sounds like the Cardinals are kind of
your top choice, right? Whenever agency
opened, it was just Arizona or bust for
you.
>> Absolutely. It was it was really that
type of wave, you know, teams, they kind
of wait around every every signing
affects everything else. So, um they
were one of my, you know, top top uh
biders and stuff like that. You know
what I'm saying? Really only biders. So,
um that was exciting. That's what makes
me excited about it. you know, they they
believe in me. Mike believes in me. And,
you know, when he brings my my resume to
the team and tells the GM, you know, um,
Monty, you know, hey, Kendrick Bourne,
that that says a lot. It goes a long
way. That's my name. I carry my name.
So, that's that's something that I'm
proud of. I don't say that much, but
because it's got me here. So, now it's
time to prove it after.